generateuk.co.uk 2009-12-04

# Digital Marketing Agency Berkshire - Privacy Policy

_Last modified: July 15 2008_

At Generate UK we recognise the privacy of our visitors is of utmost important. The following Privacy Policy applies to all of the web sites, services and products owned and operated by Generate UK Limited.  
Should you have any queries relating to our Privacy Policy, please [contact us here](http://generateuk.co.uk/index.php/Generate-UK-Ltd.html) or you can write to us at the address detailed at the end of this page.

## Providing visitors with anonymous access

The Generate UK Ltd website is available to browse without disclosing any personal data.   
Automatic collection of information

We use cookies for the sole purpose of the technical operation of some areas of our website. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifying information.

If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, it is possible to change the configuration of your browser to either warn you when you receive a cookie, or to automatically reject them. You may find, however, that disabling cookies means certain areas of the site do not function correctly.  
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

#### **Data collection and use**  

We collect personal data that you volunteer while using our website or whilst conducting a commercial relationship with us. This is information that you have submitted to us and it will not be shared with third parties.

To keep our databases accurate, we may also collect information about you from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

We may use your personal data for research and development, customer administration and marketing. Should any information be passed to us from within your company that relates to you, we will use this information as a referral and contact you if appropriate.

**Confidentiality & security**

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:  

  1. Unauthorised access 
  2. Improper use or disclosure 
  3. Unauthorised modification 
  4. Unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All of our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to state institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.  
Access to the personal data we may hold about you 

You are entitled by law to request a copy of any personal data we hold about you. If you would like to know whether we hold personal information about you, or to request a copy, you can ask us by sending an email to [info@generateuk.co.uk](mailto:info@generateuk.co.uk)

Alternatively, you are welcome to write to us using the address at the end of this page.

In receipt of your request, we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about you. It is our aim to achieve this within a week, if this is not possible then we will communicate this with you. Please note that to enable us to release any data, it is likely that we will require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  1. Completed 
  2. Rectified or amended 
  3. Erased 

### The services and links of our website  

Our website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.  
Where our website contains links to third party sites, Generate UK Ltd is not responsible for the privacy policies of those sites.

**Privacy compliance**

Our privacy policy is compliant with the Data Protection Act 1998 UK, and we are committed to a procedure of self-assessment to ensure we continue to comply.

**Amendments to our policy**

We reserve the right to make amendments to our privacy policy in the future so that we continue to comply with the law and best practice. If we do so, we will advise you of changes via our website.

**Queries**

If you have any other queries relating to your privacy and the use of your personal data, please contact:

Privacy Matters  
C/O Generate UK Ltd  
The Cornes  
Winchester  
SO22 5DS
